Guide to the Joseph L. Fisher papers, 1962-1991
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 2: U.S. House of Representatives, 1974-1981
  - ADMINISTRATION TAX PACKAGE. (Folder 14, Box 6)
  - ADMINISTRATION TAX PACKAGE. (Folder 15, Box 6)
  - ADMINISTRATION TAX PACKAGE. (Folder 16, Box 6)
  - ADMINISTRATION TAX PACKAGE. (Folder 17, Box 6)
  - ADMINISTRATION TAX PACKAGE. (Folder 1, Box 7)
  - ADMINISTRATION TAX PACKAGE. (Folder 2, Box 7)
  - FISHER AMENDMENT TO REVENUE ACT OF 1978. (Folder 3, Box 7)
  - REVENUE ACT OF 1978. (Folder 4, Box 7)
  - TAX ADMINISTRATION. (Folder 5, Box 7)
  - 1975 - WAYS PLUS MEANS COMMITTEE TAX POLICY AS FISCAL POLICY. (Folder 6, Box 7)
  - 1975 - WAYS PLUS MEANS COMMITTEE FORD ECONOMIC PROGRAM. (Folder 7, Box 7)
  - 1980 TAX CUT BILL. (Folder 8, Box 7)
  - 1978 TAX CUT BILL. (Folder 9, Box 7)
  - KEMP - ROTH TAX CUT. (Folder 10, Box 7)
  - KEMP - ROTH TAX CUTS. (Folder 11, Box 7)
  - KEMP - ROTH. (Folder 12, Box 7)
  - WAYS PLUS MEANS COMMITTEE FORD TAX CUT PROPOSAL. (Folder 13, Box 7)
  - VALUE ADDED TAX. (Folder 14, Box 7)
  - VALUE ADDED TAXES. (Folder 15, Box 7)
  - 1978 TAX REFORM BILL (BACKGROUND INFORMATION). (Folder 1, Box 8)
  - TAX REFORM. (Folder 2, Box 8)
  - TAX REFORM (FROM MISCELLANEOUS FILE). (Folder 3, Box 8)
  - TAX REFORM ( FROM MISCELLANEOUS FILES). (Folder 4, Box 8)
  - TED TAYLOR SEMINAR TAX REFORM. (Folder 5, Box 8)
  - TAX REFORM ACT OF 1976. (Folder 6, Box 8)
  - TAX REFORM ACT 1976. (Folder 7, Box 8)
  - TAX REFORM ACT OF 1976. (Folder 8, Box 8)
  - WAYS PLUS MEANS CARRYOVER BASIS. (Folder 9, Box 8)
  - WAYS PLUS MEANS CARRYOVER BASIS. (Folder 10, Box 8)
  - TAX REFORM ACT OF 1976 (CARRYOVER BASIS). (Folder 11, Box 8)
  - CARRYOVER BASIS. (Folder 12, Box 8)
  - TAX REFORM OF 1975. (Folder 13, Box 8)
  - TAX REFORM ACT OF 1975. (Folder 14, Box 8)
  - 1975 WAYS PLUS MEANS COMMITTEE TAX REFORM. (Folder 15, Box 8)
  - 1975 WAYS PLUS MEANS COMMITTEE TAX REFORM. (Folder 16, Box 8)
  - FRESHMAN DEMOCRATS TAX REFORM COMMITTEE. (Folder 17, Box 8)
  - REGULATORY REFORM. (Folder 18, Box 8)
  - 1975 WAYS PLUS MEANS COMMITTEE TAX REDUCTION ACT (Folder 19, Box 8)
  - 1975 - WAYS PLUS MEANS COMMITTEE TAX REDUCTION ACT. (Folder 20, Box 8)
  - TAX SIMPLIFICATION. (Folder 21, Box 8)
  - 1975 WAYS PLUS MEANS COMMITTEE TAX SIMPLIFICATION. (Folder 22, Box 8)
  - 1975 WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE TAX SHELTERS. (Folder 1, Box 9)
  - TAX SHELTERS, MINIMUM TAX, AND ALLOCATION OF DEDUCTIONS. (Folder 2, Box 1)
  - TAX SHELTERS, MINIMUM TAX, AND ALLOCATION OF DEDUCTION. (Folder 3, Box 9)
  - CHARITABLE CONTRIBUTIONS. (Folder 4, Box 9)
  - FISHER - CONABLE. (Folder 5, Box 9)
  - FISHER - CONABLE. (Folder 6, Box 9)
  - CHARITABLE CONTRIBUTIONS - TAX EXEMPT ORGANIZATIONS. (Folder 7, Box 9)
  - CHARITABLE CONTRIBUTIONS - TAX EXEMPT ORGANIZATIONS. (Folder 8, Box 9)
  - CHARITABLE CONTRIBUTIONS. (Folder 9, Box 9)
  - CHARITABLE CONTRIBUTIONS. (Folder 10, Box 9)
  - 1975 - WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE CHARITABLE CONTRIBUTIONS / NON - PROFIT ORGANIZATIONS. (Folder 11, Box 9)
  - UTILITY TAX DEDUCTION BILL. (Folder 12, Box 9)
  - TUITION TAX CREDIT. (Folder 13, Box 9)
  - TUITION TAX CREDIT. (Folder 14, Box 9)
  - TUITION TAX CREDIT. (Folder 15, Box 9)
  - DISABILITY / SICK PAY EXCLUSION. (Folder 1, Box 10)
  - DISABILITY / SICK PAY EXCLUSION. (Folder 2, Box 10)
  - DISABILITY / SICK PAY EXCLUSION. (Folder 3, Box 10)
  - DISABILITY / SICK PAY EXCLUSION. (Folder 4, Box 10)
  - THE CREDIT FOR ELDERLY. (Folder 5, Box 10)
  - THE CREDIT FOR ELDERLY. (Folder 6, Box 10)
  - RETIREMENT INCOME CREDIT. (Folder 7, Box 10)
  - 1975 - WAYS AND MEANS RETIREMENT INCOME CREDIT / FEDERAL PENSION. (Folder 8, Box 10)
  - RETIREMENT INCOME CREDIT. (Folder 10, Box 10)
  - RETIREMENT INCOME CREDIT. (Folder 11, Box 10)
  - RETIREMENT INCOME CREDIT. (Folder 12, Box 10)
  - TAX - EXEMPT BONDS #1. (Folder 13, Box 10)
  - TAX - EXEMPT BOND #2. (Folder 14, Box 10)
  - 1975 - WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE DEDUCTION FOR UTILITY TAXES. (Folder 15, Box 10)
  - CAPITAL FORMATION. (Folder 16, Box 10)
  - CAPITAL FORMATION TAX FORCE. (Folder 17, Box 10)
  - CAPITAL FORMATION FOR "LITTLE GUY" SAVINGS /EPSONS/PENSIONS. (Folder 18, Box 10)
  - CAPITAL FORMATION FOR "LITTLE GUY" SAVINGS /EPSONS/PENSIONS. (Folder 19, Box 10)
  - 1975 - WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE CAPITAL INVESTMENT / CORPORATE INCOME. (Folder 1, Box 11)
  - 1975 - WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE CAPITAL INVESTMENT / CORPORATE INCOME. (Folder 2, Box 11)
  - WITHHOLDING TAX ON DIVIDENDS AND INTEREST. (Folder 3, Box 11)
  - CAPITAL COST RECOVERY. (Folder 4, Box 11)
  - CAPITAL COST RECOVERY. (Folder 5, Box 11)
  - CAPITAL COST RECOVERY. (Folder 6, Box 11)
  - GROOM BILL. (Folder 7, Box 11)
  - TAX TREATMENTS OF AMERICANS LIVING ABROAD. (Folder 8, Box 11)
  - TAXATION OF FOREIGN INCOME. (Folder 9, Box 11)
  - TAXATION OF FOREIGN INCOME. (Folder 10, Box 11)
  - TAXATION OF FOREIGN INCOME. (Folder 11, Box 11)
  - CAPITAL GAINS ON FOREIGNERS. (Folder 12, Box 11)
  - CAPITAL GAINS ON FOREIGNERS. (Folder 13, Box 11)
  - SAVINGS PLUS LOAN ISSUES. (Folder 14, Box 11)
  - BUSINESS. (Folder 15, Box 11)
  - SMALL BUSINESS. (Folder 16, Box 11)
  - SMALL BUSINESS MATERIAL. (Folder 17, Box 11)
  - SMALL BUSINESS. (Folder 18, Box 11)
  - TAX TREATMENT OF SMALL BUSINESS INVESTMENT COMPANIES. (Folder 19, Box 11)
  - INDEPENDENT CONTRACTOR. (Folder 20, Box 11)
  - TAX RELIEF FOR RENTERS. (Folder 21, Box 11)
  - DEDUCTIONS FOR RENTERS. (Folder 22, Box 11)
  - TAX RELIEF FOR RENTERS. (Folder 23, Box 11)
  - TAX RELIEF FOR RENTERS. (Folder 24, Box 11)
  - TAX CREDIT FOR RENTERS. (Folder 25, Box 11)
  - TENANTS. (Folder 26, Box 11)
  - TENANTS TAX RELIEF BILL. (Folder 27, Box 11)
  - TOMARO (CONDOMINIUMS). (Folder 1, Box 12)
  - TOMARO (CONDOMINIUMS). (Folder 2, Box 12)
  - CONDOMINIUM CONVERSION SEMINAR - OCTOBER 22, 1980 8:00 PM. (Folder 3, Box 12)
  - CONDOMINIUM CONVERSION SEMINAR - OCTOBER 22, 1980 8:00 PM. (Folder 4, Box 12)
  - 1975 - WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE TAXATION ON CONDOMINIUM ASSOCIATIONS. (Folder 5, Box 12)
  - SALE OF RESIDENCE. (Folder 6, Box 12)
  - IRS PROPOSED REGULATIONS ON DWELLINGS. (Folder 7, Box 12)
  - NOISY AIRCRAFT REVENUE PLUS ACT OF 1978. (Folder 8, Box 12)
  - 96th CONGRESS - FISHER BILL H.R. 8231 - PAYMENTS - IN - LIEU - OF - TAXES. (Folder 9, Box 12)
  - MORTGAGE REVENUE BONDS H.R. 3712. (Folder 10, Box 12)
  - LOCAL PROPERTY TAX. (Folder 11, Box 12)
  - TED TAYLOR SEMINARS CONDOMINIUM CONVERSIONS SEMINAR. (Folder 12, Box 12)
  - TAX TREATMENT OF SINGLE TAXPAYERS. (Folder 13, Box 12)
  - 1975 - WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE TAX TREATMENT OF SINGLE PERSONS. (Folder 14, Box 12)
  - 1975 - WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE TAX TREATMENT OF SINGLE PERSONS. (Folder 15, Box 12)
  - MARRIAGE PENALTY TAX. (Folder 16, Box 12)
  - MARRIED/ SINGLE TAXPAYERS. (Folder 17, Box 12)
  - TAX TREATMENT OF MARRIED COUPLES. (Folder 18, Box 12)
  - 1975 - WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE TAX TREATMENT OF 2 - EARNER FAMILIES. (Folder 19, Box 12)
  - 1975 - WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE TAX TREATMENT OF 2 - EARNER FAMILIES. (Folder 20, Box 12)
  - TAX EXEMPT STATUS (PRIVATE SCHOOLS) WHO ENGAGE IN RACIAL DISCRIMINATORY PRACTICES. (Folder 21, Box 12)
  - TAX BREAK FOR TUITION. (Folder 22, Box 12)
  - FISHER ESTATE TAX BILL. (Folder 23, Box 12)
  - FISHER ESTATE TAX BILL. (Folder 24, Box 12)
  - 1975 - WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE ESTATE TAX. (Folder 25, Box 12)
  - 1975 - WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE ESTATE TAX. (Folder 1, Box 13)
  - PENSION, PROFIT - SHARING, ETC. (Folder 2, Box 13)
  - PENSION, PROFIT - S, H.R. 10, IRA ECT. (Folder 3, Box 13)
  - 1975 - WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE PENSIONS / IRA'S/ KEOGH. (Folder 4, Box 13)
  - 1975 - WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE PENSIONS / IRA'S/ KEOGH. (Folder 5, Box 13)
  - COMMON - FISHER MODIFIED I.R.A. BILL. (Folder 6, Box 13)
  - 1975 - WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE CHILD CARE/ DEPENDENT CARE. (Folder 7, Box 13)
  - TAXES - DAY CARE CENTRE. (Folder 8, Box 13)
  - TED TAYLOR SEMINAR HOSPITAL COST CONTAINMENT SEMINAR. (Folder 9, Box 13)
  - NATIONAL HEALTH INSURANCE AND COST CONTAINMENT. (Folder 10, Box 13)
  - NATIONAL HEALTH INSURANCE AND COST CONTAINMENT. (Folder 11, Box 13)
  - NATIONAL HEALTH INSURANCE AND COST CONTAINMENT. (Folder 12, Box 13)
  - REAL WAGE INSURANCE. (Folder 13, Box 13)
  - REAL WAGE INSURANCE. (Folder 14, Box 13)
  - DISABILITY PAY EXCLUSION. (Folder 15, Box 13)
  - DISABILITY / SICK - PAY. (Folder 16, Box 13)
  - 1975 - WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE DISABILITY TAX EXEMPTIONS. (Folder 17, Box 13)
  - 1975 - WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE DISABILITY TAX EXEMPTIONS. (Folder 18, Box 13)
  - 1975 - WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE DISABILITY TAX EXEMPTIONS. (Folder 19, Box 13)
  - HUMPHERY - HAWKINS BILL. (Folder 1, Box 14)
  - ISSUES - UNEMPLOYMENT. (Folder 2, Box 14)
  - ENERGY - 96th CONGRESS. (Folder 3, Box 14)
  - ENERGY (CORRESPONDENCE - OCTOBER TO SEPTEMBER, 1977). (Folder 4, Box 14)
  - ENERGY (CORRESPONDENCE AUGUST, 1977). (Folder 5, Box 14)
  - ENERGY (CORRESPONDENCE - JULY TO JANUARY, 1977). (Folder 6, Box 14)
  - ENERGY ( FORM MISCELLANEOUS FILE). (Folder 7, Box 14)
  - WAYS AND MEANS - ENERGY (CORRESPONDENCE FEBRUARY TO JANUARY, 1975) (Folder 8, Box 14)
  - WAYS AND MEANS - ENERGY (CORRESPONDENCE - MARCH, 1975). (Folder 9, Box 14)
  - WAYS AND MEANS - ENERGY. (Folder 10, Box 14)
  - WAYS AND MEANS - ENERGY (CORRESPONDENCE - MAY, 1975). (Folder 11, Box 14)
  - WAYS AND MEANS - ENERGY (CORRESPONDENCE - JUNE, 1975). (Folder 12, Box 14)
  - WAYS AND MEANS - ENERGY (CORRESPONDENCE - SEPTEMBER TO JULY, 1975). (Folder 13, Box 14)
  - ENERGY (GENERAL - 1978 TO 1975). (Folder 14, Box 14)
  - TED TAYLOR SEMINAR ENERGY - TAX ASPECTS. (Folder 15, Box 14)
  - 1977 - AD HOC ENERGY COMMITTEE (CORRESPONDENCE - MAY TO APRIL, 1977). (Folder 16, Box 15)
  - 1977 - AD HOC ENERGY COMMITTEE (CORRESPONDENCE - JUNE, 1977). (Folder 17, Box 14)
  - AD HOC ENERGY COMMITTEE (CORRESPONDENCE JANUARY, 1978 TO AUGUST, 1977). (Folder 18, Box 14)
  - ENERGY TRUST FUND PART 1 (GENERAL - AUGUST TO JANUARY 1979). (Folder 1, Box 15)
  - ENERGY TRUST FUND PART I (GENERAL - MARCH, 1980 - SEPTEMBER, 1979). (Folder 2, Box 15)
  - ENERGY TRUST FUND PART I (GENERAL - 1980 - 1979). (Folder 3, Box 15)
  - ENERGY TRUST FUND PART I (GENERAL - 1980 - 1979). (Folder 4, Box 15)
  - ENERGY TRUST FUND PART I (GENERAL - 1980). (Folder 5, Box 15)
  - ENERGY TAX OF 1977. (Folder 6, Box 15)
  - ENERGY TAX ACT OF 1977. (Folder 7, Box 15)
  - 1975 WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE RE: H.R. 6860, ENERGY CONSERVATION BILL. (Folder 8, Box 15)
  - ENERGY - MISCELLANEOUS: GASAHOL, THERMOSTATS, MOODY MOBILE. (Folder 9, Box 15)
  - GASOLINE ( GENERAL - 1980 - 79). (Folder 10, Box 15)
  - GASOLINE RATIONING MATERIAL ( GENERAL 1980). (Folder 11, Box 15)
  - OIL ( GENERAL - 1979). (Folder 12, Box 15)
  - OIL IMPORT FEE (GENERAL - 1980). (Folder 13, Box 15)
  - SYNFUELS (GENERAL - 1980). (Folder 14, Box 15)
  - CO - GENERATION MATERIAL. (Folder 15, Box 15)
  - O' LEARY MEETING ON GASOLINE (GENERAL - 1979). (Folder 16, Box 15)
  - COMMUTER TAX (GENERAL - 1978 TO 1976). (Folder 17, Box 15)
  - ENERGY MOBILIZATION BOARD. (Folder 1, Box 16)
  - WINDFALL PROFITS TAX H.R. 3919 PART I. (Folder 2, Box 16)
  - WINDFALL PROFIT TAX ( PRESS - 1980 TO 1979). (Folder 3, Box 16)
  - BACKGROUND INFORMATION ON WINDFALL PROFITS TAX LEGISLATION PART II. (Folder 4, Box 16)
  - BACKGROUND INFORMATION ON WINDFALL PROFITS TAX LEGISLATION PART II (REPORTS, COPIES OF BILL PLUS COMMITTEE - 1979). (Folder 5, Box 16)
  - CHRYSLER LOAN GUARANTEES. (Folder 6, Box 16)
  - CHRYSLER LOAN GUARANTEES. (Folder 7, Box 16)
  - GAS GUZZLER TAX AMENDMENT (GENERAL - 1976 - 75). (Folder 8, Box 16)
  - CONSERVATION EASEMENT. (Folder 9, Box 16)
  - ENVIRONMENT - ISSUES. (Folder 10, Box 16)
  - SUPERFUND (CLEARING UP TOXIC WASTE) # 1. (Folder 11, Box 16)
  - SUPERFUND (CLEANING UP TOXIC WASTE) #2. (Folder 12, Box 16)
  - POLLUTION EXCISE TAXES (GENERAL - 1976). (Folder 13, Box 16)
  - TAXES ON POLLUTION (GENERAL - 1976 - 75). (Folder 14, Box 16)
  - TAXES ON POLLUTION (GENERAL - JULY, 1975). (Folder 15, Box 16)
  - D.C. PROFESSIONALS TAX (CORRESPONDENCE - 1975). (Folder 1, Box 17)
  - D.C. PROFESSIONALS TAX (GENERAL 1975 - 1976). (Folder 2, Box 17)
  - WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE - WILLIAMSBURG BILL (CORRESPONDENCE - 1975). (Folder 3, Box 17)
  - NORFOLK PLUS WESTERN BILL (GENERAL - 1980). (Folder 4, Box 17)
  - MERCHANT MARINE BILL (MEMO - 1980). (Folder 5, Box 17)
  - AIRPLANE TAX BILL (CORRESPONDENCE - 1980). (Folder 6, Box 17)
  - ADOPTION BILL (GENERAL - 1980 TO 1979). (Folder 7, Box 17)
  - PROFESSIONAL SPORTS SELECT SUBCOMMITTEE PART I (GENERAL - 1976). (Folder 8, Box 17)
  - PROFESSIONAL SPORTS SELECT SUBCOMMITTEE PART II (GENERAL - 1976). (Folder 9, Box 17)
  - PROFESSIONAL SPORTS (CORRESPONDENCE - 1976). (Folder 10, Box 17)
  - WORLD PEACE TAX FUND (FROM MISCELLANEOUS FILE) (CORRESPONDENCE 1978). (Folder 11, Box 17)
  - WORLD PEACE TAX FUND (FROM MISCELLANEOUS FILE) (CORRESPONDENCE 1977). (Folder 12, Box 17)
  - WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE WORLD PEACE TAX FUND BILL (CORRESPONDENCE 1976 TO 1975). (Folder 13, Box 17)
  - 1980 - TRADE: COMMODITIES MEAT. (Folder 14, Box 17)
  - 1980 - WAYS AND MEANS: TRADE EASTERN EUROPE TRIP. (Folder 15, Box 17)
  - 1980 - WAYS AND MEANS: TRADE CZECHOSLOVAKIAN GOLD. (Folder 16, Box 17)
  - 1980 - WAYS AND MEANS: TRADE MISCELLANEOUS. (Folder 17, Box 17)
  - TED TAYLOR SEMINAR MULTINATION TRADE NEGOTIATIONS (GENERAL - FEBRUARY 26, 1979). (Folder 18, Box 17)
  - TED TAYLOR SEMINAR TRADE (CORRESPONDENCE MAY 9, 1977). (Folder 19, Box 17)
  - 1980 - WAYS AND MEANS PUBLIC ASSISTANCE. (Folder 20, Box 17)
  - WELFARE (CLIPPINGS - 1979 TO 1977). (Folder 21, Box 17)
  - 1979 - WAYS AND MEANS: TRADE ADJUSTMENT ASSISTANCE. (Folder 22, Box 17)
  - 1979 - MTNs TED TAYLOR SEMINAR. (Folder 23, Box 17)
  - SPEECH AT INTERNATIONAL MANAGEMENT AND DEVELOPMENT INSTITUTE (FEBRUARY 6, 1979). (Folder 24, Box 17)
  - 1980 - TRADE: COMMODITIES SUGAR. (Folder 25, Box 17)
  - ISSUES - TRADE. (Folder 26, Box 17)
  - 1979 - WAYS AND MEANS RE: WELFARE AND SOCIAL SECURITY INSURANCE (CORRESPONDENCE - 1979). (Folder 27, Box 17)
  - 1978 - WAYS AND MEANS PUBLIC ASSISTANCE. (Folder 28, Box 17)
  - WAYS AND MEANS WELFARE REFORM MATERIAL (GENERAL - 1978 - 77). (Folder 29, Box 17)
  - 1978 - WAYS AND MEANS RE: WELFARE PLUS PUBLIC ASSISTANCE (CORRESPONDENCE - 1978 TO 1977). (Folder 30, Box 17)
  - 1977 - WAYS AND MEANS PUBLIC ASSISTANCE. (Folder 31, Box 17)
  - 1979 - WAYS AND MEANS RE: SOCIAL SECURITY DISABILITY (GENERAL - 1979). (Folder 1, Box 18)
  - TED TAYLOR SEMINARS SOCIAL SECURITY DISABILITY INSURANCE (GENERAL - MARCH 12, 1979). (Folder 2, Box 18)
  - 1979 - WAYS AND MEANS UNIVERSAL COVERAGE (CORRESPONDENCE APRIL TO JANUARY). (Folder 3, Box 18)
  - 1979 - WAYS AND MEANS UNIVERSAL COVERAGE (CORRESPONDENCE - DECEMBER TO MAY). (Folder 4, Box 18)
  - 1978 - WAYS AND MEANS SOCIAL SECURITY (CORRESPONDENCE). (Folder 5, Box 18)
  - WAYS AND MEANS SOCIAL SECURITY H.R. 9346. (Folder 6, Box 18)
  - WAYS AND MEANS SOCIAL SECURITY (CLIPPINGS - 1977). (Folder 7, Box 18)
  - 1977 - WAYS AND MEANS SOCIAL SECURITY. (Folder 8, Box 18)
  - 1977 - WAYS AND MEANS SOCIAL SECURITY (CORRESPONDENCE - OCTOBER 21, 1977). (Folder 9, Box 18)
  - 1977 - WAYS AND MEANS SOCIAL SECURITY. (Folder 10, Box 18)
  - 1977 - WAYS MEANS SOCIAL SECURITY. (Folder 11, Box 18)
  - 1977 - WAYS AND MEANS FISHER AMENDMENT TO SOCIAL SECURITY H.R. 9346 ( GENERAL). (Folder 12, Box 18)
  - 1977 - WAYS AND MEANS FISHER AMENDMENT TO SOCIAL SECURITY H.R. 9346. (Folder 13, Box 18)
  - 1977 - WAYS AND MEANS FISHER AMENDMENT TO SOCIAL SECURITY H.R. 9346 (CORRESPONDENCE). (Folder 14, Box 18)
  - 1977 - WAYS AND MEANS SOCIAL SECURITY AND CIVIL SERVICE RETIREMENT (CORRESPONDENCE - OCTOBER 5, 1977). (Folder 15, Box 18)
  - 1977 - WAYS AND MEANS SOCIAL SECURITY (CORRESPONDENCE - SEPTEMBER 21, 1977). (Folder 16, Box 18)
  - BUDGET - MISCELLANEOUS # 1. (Folder 17, Box 18)
  - BUDGET - MISCELLANEOUS #2. (Folder 18, Box 18)
  - BUDGET RESOLUTION FY 1980 (GENERAL - 1979). (Folder 19, Box 18)
  - RECONCILIATION TAX MATTERS. (Folder 1, Box 19)
  - RECONCILIATION TAX MATTERS. (Folder 2, Box 19)
  - 1980 CENSUS APPOINTMENTS #1. (Folder 3, Box 19)
  - 1980 CENSUS APPOINTMENTS #2. (Folder 4, Box 19)
  - APPROPRIATIONS BILL MATERIAL (GENERAL - 1980 TO 1979). (Folder 5, Box 19)
  - FIRST BUDGET RESOLUTION FOR F.Y. 1981. (Folder 6, Box 19)
  - BUDGET COMMITTEE (GENERAL - 1980 - 1979). (Folder 7, Box 19)
  - ANTI INFLATION GROUP AND BILL (GENERAL 1979 to 80). (Folder 8, Box 19)
  - INFLATION (GENERAL - 1980 TO 1979). (Folder 9, Box 19)
  - BUDGET COMMITTEE (GENERAL - 1980 TO 1975). (Folder 10, Box 19)
  - BUDGET (CLIPPINGS - 179 TO 1975). (Folder 11, Box 19)
  - FISHER SUBSTITUTION TO SECOND BUDGET RESOLUTION FOR FISCAL YEAR 1980 (NEVER OFFERED). (Folder 12, Box 19)
  - BUDGET ( GENERAL - 1978). (Folder 13, Box 19)
  - 1978 BUDGET LETTERS (JUNE TO JANUARY, 1978). (Folder 14, Box 19)
  - 1978 - BUDGET LETTERS (NOVEMBER TO JULY, 1978). (Folder 15, Box 19)
  - BUDGET COMMITTEE ART'S LETTERS (CORRESPONDENCE NOVEMBER TO JANUARY, 1978). (Folder 1, Box 20)
  - BUDGET COMMITTEE ART'S LETTERS (CORRESPONDENCE JANUARY, 1979 TO DECEMBER, 1978). (Folder 2, Box 20)
  - THE GOVERNMENT AND ECONOMY (ARTICLES - 1978 TO 1977). (Folder 3, Box 20)
  - THE GOVERNMENT AND ECONOMY (ARTICLES - 1978 TO 1977). (Folder 4, Box 20)
  - INFLATION ( PRESS, ANALYSIS, REPORT - 1978 TO 1977). (Folder 5, Box 20)
  - INFLATION ( PRESS, ANALYSIS, REPORT - 1978 TO 1977). (Folder 6, Box 20)
  - CONGRESSIONAL PROPOSALS ON INFLATION ( 1978 - 77). (Folder 7, Box 20)
  - BUDGET PROJECTIONS (GENERAL - 1978 TO 1977). (Folder 8, Box 20)
  - BUDGET COMMITTEE STATE OF ECONOMY REPORTS ( GENERAL 1977). (Folder 9, Box 20)
  - TED TAYLOR SEMINAR ECONOMY (GENERAL - JANUARY 4, 1977). (Folder 10, Box 20)
  - TED TAYLOR SEMINAR B-1 BOMBER (GENERAL - APRIL 19, 1977). (Folder 11, Box 20)
  - IRS APPROPRIATE AMENDMENT ( GENERAL - 1980). (Folder 12, Box 20)
  - BUDGET: JLF AMENDMENT DOLLAR INFORMATION (GENERAL - 1976 TO 1975). (Folder 13, Box 20)
  - 1980 - ARMED SERVICES RE: DIVORCED SPOUSES (GENERAL). (Folder 14, Box 20)
  - 1980 - POST OFFICES PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: COST OF LIVING TWICE YEARLY. (Folder 15, Box 20)
  - EARTH DAY (POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE). (Folder 16, Box 20)
  - FEDERAL EMPLOYEES - 96th CONGRESS (GENERAL - 1980 TO 1979). (Folder 17, Box 20)
  - 1979 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE PAY DELAYS (CORRESPONDENCE). (Folder 18, Box 20)
  - 1979 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: FEDERAL PAY. (Folder 19, Box 20)
  - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE FEDERAL COMPENSATION. (Folder 1, Box 21)
  - 1978 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: CIVIL SERVICE REORGANIZATION (CORRESPONDENCE - APRIL TO JANUARY). (Folder 2, Box 21)
  - 1978 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: CIVIL SERVICE REORGANIZATION (CORRESPONDENCE JUNE - MAY). (Folder 3, Box 21)
  - 1978 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: CIVIL SERVICE REORGANIZATION (CORRESPONDENCE AUGUST - JULY). (Folder 4, Box 21)
  - 1978 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: CIVIL SERVICE REORGANIZATION (CORRESPONDENCE DECEMBER - OCTOBER). (Folder 5, Box 21)
  - 1978 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: CIVIL SERVICE REORGANIZATION. (Folder 6, Box 21)
  - 1978 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: CIVIL SERVICE REFORM. (Folder 7, Box 21)
  - 1979 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: RETIRES COST - OF - LIVING RAISE. (Folder 8, Box 21)
  - CIVIL SERVICE REPORT. (Folder 9, Box 21)
  - FEDERAL EMPLOYEES. (Folder 10, Box 21)
  - 1977 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: HATCH ACT. (Folder 11, Box 21)
  - 1977 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: HATCH ACT. (Folder 12, Box 21)
  - 1977 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: HATCH ACT. (Folder 13, Box 21)
  - 1977 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: HATCH ACT. (Folder 14, Box 21)
  - 1977 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: HATCH ACT. (Folder 15, Box 21)
  - 1977 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE COMMITTEE EMPLOYEE POLITICAL RIGHTS INFORMATION. (Folder 16, Box 21)
  - 1977 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE COMMITTEE EMPLOYEE POLITICAL RIGHTS INFORMATION. (Folder 17, Box 21)
  - 1977 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: FEDERAL RETIREMENT. (Folder 18, Box 21)
  - 1976 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: FEDERAL RETIREMENT (CORRESPONDENCE JULY TO JANUARY, 1976) (Folder 1, Box 22)
  - 1976 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: FEDERAL RETIREMENT (COVER LETTER MAY 11, 1976 FIELD WITH A COVER LETTER FOR JUNE 28, 1976). (Folder 2, Box 22)
  - 1976 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: FEDERAL RETIREMENT (COVER LETTER JUNE 28, 1976). (Folder 3, Box 22)
  - 1976 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: FEDERAL RETIREMENT (COVER LETTER SEPT. 28, 1976). (Folder 4, Box 22)
  - 1976 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEE POLITICAL RIGHTS (CORRESPONDENCE 1976 TO 1975). (Folder 5, Box 22)
  - 1975 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE 1% FACTOR. (Folder 6, Box 22)
  - (Folder 7, Box 22)
  - 1977 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: HATCH ACT (COVER LETTER OF JUNE 15, 1977). (Folder 8, Box 22)
  - 1977 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: HATCH ACT (COVER LETTER OF JUNE 15, 1977). (Folder 9, Box 22)
  - 1977 - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE RE: HATCH ACT (CORRESPONDENCE - 1976 TO 1975). (Folder 10, Box 22)
  - 1980 - INDOCHINA REFUGEES. (Folder 11, Box 22)
  - TED TAYLOR SEMINARS INDOCHINESE REFUGEES (GENERAL - FEBRUARY 12, 1980). (Folder 12, Box 22)
  - TED TAYLOR SEMINARS INDOCHINESE REFUGEES (GENERAL - FEBRUARY 12, 1980). (Folder 13, Box 22)
  - DEFENCE VOTES - ORIGINALS. (Folder 14, Box 22)
  - DEFENSE AND MILITARY. (Folder 15, Box 22)
  - FOREIGN POLICY. (Folder 16, Box 22)
  - DIPLOMATIC (JEAN McDONALD FROM MIKKI). (Folder 17, Box 22)
  - INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS 1978 - DIPLOMATIC IMMUNITY. (Folder 18, Box 22)
  - INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS 1978 - DIPLOMATIC IMMUNITY. (Folder 19, Box 22)
  - INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS 1978 - DIPLOMATIC IMMUNITY. (Folder 20, Box 22)
  - DIPLOMACY. (Folder 21, Box 22)
  - TED TAYLOR SEMINAR INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS RE: PANAMA CANAL. (Folder 22, Box 22)
  - TED TAYLOR SEMINAR PANAMA TREATY SEMINAR. (Folder 23, Box 22)
  - DIPLOMATIC IMMUNITY. (Folder 1, Box 23)
  - McGUIRE, SCOTT - DIPLOMATIC IMMUNITY. (Folder 2, Box 23)
  - LIABILITY INSURANCE FOR DIPLOMATS. (Folder 3, Box 23)
  - H.R. 1484 - DIPLOMATIC IMMUNITY. (Folder 4, Box 23)
  - TED TAYLOR SEMINAR UNDOCUMENTED ALIENS SEMINAR. (Folder 5, Box 23)
  - 1977 - JUDICIARY COMMITTEE RE: ILLEGAL ALIENS (TED TAYLOR SEMINAR). (Folder 6, Box 23)
  - ISSUES - CRIMINAL JUSTICE. (Folder 7, Box 23)
  - FAIRFAX CITY REIMBURSEMENT. (Folder 8, Box 23)
  - 1980 - JUDICIARY FAIRFAX CITY. (Folder 9, Box 23)
  - 1980 - JUDICIARY FAIRFAX CITY. (Folder 10, Box 23)
  - 1977 - JUDICIARY COMMITTEE CIVIL PLUS CONSTITUTIONAL RIGHTS SUBCOMMITTEE. (Folder 11, Box 23)
  - 95th AND 94th CONGRESS - ABORTION (GENERAL - 1978 TO 1975). (Folder 12, Box 23)
  - THE ENCOURAGING BILL. (Folder 13, Box 23)
  - 1979 - JUDICIARY ALTERNATIVE TO ABORTION. (Folder 14, Box 23)
  - 1979 - JUDICIARY ALTERNATIVE TO ABORTION. (Folder 15, Box 23)
  - 1979 - JUDICIARY ALTERNATIVE TO ABORTION. (Folder 16, Box 23)
  - FAIR HOUSING. (Folder 17, Box 23)
  - JUDICIARY - SPEECH ON PATENTS. (Folder 18, Box 23)
  - HEW - KIDNEY DIALYSIS. (Folder 19, Box 23)
  - BILINGUAL EDUCATION. (Folder 20, Box 23)
  - EDUCATION - ISSUE PAPER # 7. (Folder 21, Box 23)
  - MISCELLANEOUS CLIPS. (Folder 22, Box 23)
  - WOMEN. (Folder 23, Box 23)
  - MISCELLANEOUS. (Folder 24, Box 23)
  - OLDER AMERICANS. (Folder 25, Box 23)
  - TED TAYLOR SEMINAR FAMILY AND THE NEIGHBORHOOD. (Folder 26, Box 23)
  - TED TAYLOR SEMINAR THE FAMILY. (Folder 27, Box 23)
  - HEALTH ISSUES. (Folder 28, Box 23)
  - LABOR ISSUES. (Folder 29, Box 23)
  - FAMILY AND NEIGHBORHOOD - ISSUES. (Folder 30, Box 23)
  - ANIMALS. (Folder 31, Box 23)
  - (VIRGINIA) PUBLIC WORKS I-66 INFORMATION. (Folder 1, Box 24)
  - 1980 VIRGINIA I-66. (Folder 2, Box 24)
  - I-66. (Folder 3, Box 24)
  - I-66 (Folder 4, Box 24)